<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">纸糊阅读</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material 就是隐喻.\n\n"

        "物质隐喻是合理空间和运动系统的统一理论。"
        "该材料以触觉现实为基础，灵感来自对纸张和墨水的研究，但技术先进，对想象力和魔力开放。\n"
        "材料的表面和边缘提供了实际的视觉提示。熟悉的触觉属性的使用可以帮助用户快速了解能力。然而，材料的灵活性"
        "创造了新的能力，在不违反物理规则的情况下可以取代物理世界的能力。\n"
        "光线，表面和运动的基本原理是传达物体在空间中以及彼此之间如何运动，相互作用和存在的关键。逼真的照明可以"
        "显示接缝，划分空间并指示运动部件。\n\n"

        "粗体，图形，故意。\n\n"

        "基于印刷的设计排版，网格，空间，比例，颜色和图像使用的基本要素指导视觉处理。这些元素的作用远远超过取悦"
        "眼睛。他们创建层次结构，含义和重点。故意的颜色选择，边缘到边缘的图像，大规模的排版和有意的空白区域创建了"
        "醒目的图形界面，使用户沉浸在体验中。\n"
        "对用户动作的强调使核心功能立即显而易见，并为用户提供了航路点。\n\n"

        "运动提供了意义。\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">设置</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">设置</string>
    <string name="messages_header">消息</string>
    <string name="sync_header">同步</string>
    <string name="signature_title">你的签名</string>
    <string name="reply_title">默认回复</string>
    <string name="sync_title">同步周期</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">下载附件</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">自动下载附件</string>
</resources>